var Question = require('../models').Question;

var createQuestions = function(id) {

/*---------- LEVEL 1, NOUNS ----------*/
	/* LESSON 1, Creatures of Essos */
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "havzi", "correctAnswer": "cat", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Creatures of Essos" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "zhavorsa", "correctAnswer": "dragon", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Creatures of Essos" });
	// Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "hrazef", "correctAnswer": "horse", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Creatures of Essos" });
	// Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "hlizif", "correctAnswer": "bear", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Creatures of Essos" });
	// Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "adra", "correctAnswer": "turtle", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Creatures of Essos" });
	// Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "dorvi", "correctAnswer": "goat", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Creatures of Essos" });
	// Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "eshina", "correctAnswer": "fish", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Creatures of Essos" });
	// Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "gezri", "correctAnswer": "snake", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Creatures of Essos" });
	// Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "hrakkar", "correctAnswer": "lion", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Creatures of Essos" });
	// Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "gimi", "correctAnswer": "mouse", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Creatures of Essos" });

	/* LESSON 2, Nature and Landscapes*/
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "asavva", "correctAnswer": "sky", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Nature and Landscapes" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "ashefa", "correctAnswer": "river", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Nature and Landscapes" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "athasar", "correctAnswer": "wasteland", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Nature and Landscapes" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "hranna", "correctAnswer": "grass", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Nature and Landscapes" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "daeni", "correctAnswer": "leaf", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Nature and Landscapes" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "dana", "correctAnswer": "forest clearing", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Nature and Landscapes" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "ejakh", "correctAnswer": "river bank", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Nature and Landscapes" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "fas", "correctAnswer": "cloud", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Nature and Landscapes" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "feshith", "correctAnswer": "tree", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Nature and Landscapes" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "halah", "correctAnswer": "flower", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Nature and Landscapes" });

	/* LESSON 3, Positions and Warfare */
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "vilajero", "correctAnswer": "battle", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Positions and Warfare" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "vov", "correctAnswer": "weapon", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Positions and Warfare" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "athvilajerar", "correctAnswer": "war", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Positions and Warfare" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "kohol", "correctAnswer": "bow", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Positions and Warfare" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "akkelenak", "correctAnswer": "leader", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Positions and Warfare" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "khal", "correctAnswer": "king", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Positions and Warfare" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "khaleesi", "correctAnswer": "queen", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Positions and Warfare" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "lajak", "correctAnswer": "warrior", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Positions and Warfare" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "lajasar", "correctAnswer": "army", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Positions and Warfare" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "najahheya", "correctAnswer": "victory", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Positions and Warfare" });

	/* LESSON 4, Seasons and the Elements */
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "vorsaska", "correctAnswer": "summer", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Seasons and the Elements" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "vorsa", "correctAnswer": "fire", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Seasons and the Elements" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "chafka", "correctAnswer": "autumn", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Seasons and the Elements" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "chaf", "correctAnswer": "wind", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Seasons and the Elements" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "eyel", "correctAnswer": "rain", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Seasons and the Elements" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "jesh", "correctAnswer": "ice", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Seasons and the Elements" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "aheshke", "correctAnswer": "winter", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Seasons and the Elements" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "ahesh", "correctAnswer": "snow", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Seasons and the Elements" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "eveth", "correctAnswer": "water", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Seasons and the Elements" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "eyelke", "correctAnswer": "spring", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Seasons and the Elements" });

	/* LESSON 5, Family */
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "inavva", "correctAnswer": "sister", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Family" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "ohara", "correctAnswer": "daughter", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Family" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "gaezo", "correctAnswer": "brother", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Family" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "janise", "correctAnswer": "niece", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Family" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "ave", "correctAnswer": "father", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Family" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "rizh", "correctAnswer": "son", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Family" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "kim", "correctAnswer": "ancestor", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Family" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "chiorikem", "correctAnswer": "wife", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Family" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "mai", "correctAnswer": "mother", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Family" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "mahrazhkem", "correctAnswer": "husband", "m": 1, "level": 1, "levelTitle": "Nouns", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Family" });


/*---------- LEVEL 2, NUMBERS, PRONOUNS, AND INTERJECTIONS ----------*/
	/* LESSON 1, Numbers - Part 1 */
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "at", "correctAnswer": "one", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Numbers Part 1" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "akat", "correctAnswer": "two", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Numbers Part 1" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "sen", "correctAnswer": "three", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Numbers Part 1" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "tor", "correctAnswer": "four", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Numbers Part 1" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "mek", "correctAnswer": "five", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Numbers Part 1" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "zhinda", "correctAnswer": "six", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Numbers Part 1" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "fekh", "correctAnswer": "seven", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Numbers Part 1" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "ori", "correctAnswer": "eight", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Numbers Part 1" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "qazat", "correctAnswer": "nine", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Numbers Part 1" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "thi", "correctAnswer": "ten", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Numbers Part 1" });
	
	/* LESSON 2, Numbers - Part 2 */
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "som", "correctAnswer": "zero", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Numbers Part 2" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "ken", "correctAnswer": "hundred", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Numbers Part 2" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "dalen", "correctAnswer": "thousand", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Numbers Part 2" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "yor", "correctAnswer": "million", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Numbers Part 2" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "yorosor", "correctAnswer": "infinity", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Numbers Part 2" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "chakat", "correctAnswer": "twenty", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Numbers Part 2" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "chimek", "correctAnswer": "fifty", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Numbers Part 2" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "chifekh", "correctAnswer": "seventy", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Numbers Part 2" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "chori", "correctAnswer": "eighty", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Numbers Part 2" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "chiqazat", "correctAnswer": "ninety", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Numbers Part 2" });

	/* LESSON 3, Pronouns */
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "anha", "correctAnswer": "I", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Pronouns" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "anna", "correctAnswer": "me", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Pronouns" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "me", "correctAnswer": "he, she, it", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Pronouns" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "mae", "correctAnswer": "him, her, it", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Pronouns" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "kisha", "correctAnswer": "we", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Pronouns" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "yer", "correctAnswer": "you", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Pronouns" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "yeri", "correctAnswer": "you (plural)", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Pronouns" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "ato", "correctAnswer": "something, someone", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Pronouns" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "eyak", "correctAnswer": "everyone", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Pronouns" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "vosak", "correctAnswer": "nobody", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Pronouns" });

	/* LESSON 4, Interjections */
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "m'ath", "correctAnswer": "hi", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Interjections" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "m'athchomaroon", "correctAnswer": "hi", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Interjections" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "affa", "correctAnswer": "shh", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Interjections" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "ai", "correctAnswer": "yes (formal)", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Interjections" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "m'ach", "correctAnswer": "hi", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Interjections" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "sorohis!", "correctAnswer": "halt!", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Interjections" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "graddakh!", "correctAnswer": "shit!", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Interjections" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "rai!", "correctAnswer": "hurrah!", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Interjections" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "gwe!", "correctAnswer": "let's go!", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Interjections" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "sec", "correctAnswer": "yes", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Interjections" });

	/* LESSON 5, Horse Commands */
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "reri!", "correctAnswer": "stay!", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Horse Commands" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "vitihiras", "correctAnswer": "watch!", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Horse Commands" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "affa!", "correctAnswer": "whoa!", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Horse Commands" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "soroh!", "correctAnswer": "halt!", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Horse Commands" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "hale!", "correctAnswer": "hey!", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Horse Commands" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "vikovareras!", "correctAnswer": "stay!", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Horse Commands" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "akkovaras!", "correctAnswer": "stand up!", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Horse Commands" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "akko!", "correctAnswer": "stand up!", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Horse Commands" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "hosh!", "correctAnswer": "giddyup!", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Horse Commands" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "gwe!", "correctAnswer": "here!", "m": 1, "level": 2, "levelTitle": "Numbers, Pronouns, and Interjections", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Horse Commands" });


/*---------- LEVEL 3, ADJECTIVES AND ADVERBS ----------*/
	/* LESSON 1, Colors */
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "dahaan", "correctAnswer": "green", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Colors" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "koshor", "correctAnswer": "golden", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Colors" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "kazga", "correctAnswer": "black", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Colors" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "nozhoven", "correctAnswer": "brown", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Colors" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "reaven", "correctAnswer": "purple", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Colors" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "thelis", "correctAnswer": "blue", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Colors" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "theyaven", "correctAnswer": "pink", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Colors" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "veltor", "correctAnswer": "yellow", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Colors" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "virzeth", "correctAnswer": "red", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Colors" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "zasqa", "correctAnswer": "white", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Colors" });

	/* LESSON 2, Description of a Dothraki */
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "achra", "correctAnswer": "smelly", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Description of a Dothraki" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "dik", "correctAnswer": "fast", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Description of a Dothraki" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "dis", "correctAnswer": "plain", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Description of a Dothraki" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "niqe", "correctAnswer": "rigid", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Description of a Dothraki" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "haj", "correctAnswer": "strong", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Description of a Dothraki" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "ivezh", "correctAnswer": "wild", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Description of a Dothraki" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "iste", "correctAnswer": "well tested", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Description of a Dothraki" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "najah", "correctAnswer": "victorious", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Description of a Dothraki" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "sorf", "correctAnswer": "dirty", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Description of a Dothraki" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "verven", "correctAnswer": "violent", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Description of a Dothraki" });

	/* LESSON 3, Other Useful Adjectives */
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "vezhven", "correctAnswer": "great", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Other useful Adjectives" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "zheana", "correctAnswer": "beautiful", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Other useful Adjectives" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "zhokwa", "correctAnswer": "big", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Other useful Adjectives" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "zhowak", "correctAnswer": "dangerous", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Other useful Adjectives" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "afazh", "correctAnswer": "hot", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Other useful Adjectives" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "fish", "correctAnswer": "cold", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Other useful Adjectives" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "ale", "correctAnswer": "more", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Other useful Adjectives" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "edavrasa", "correctAnswer": "useless", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Other useful Adjectives" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "ataki", "correctAnswer": "first", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Other useful Adjectives" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "nakhok", "correctAnswer": "last", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Other useful Adjectives" });

	/* LESSON 4, Adverbs - Part 1 */
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "affin", "correctAnswer": "when", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Adverbs - Part 1" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "finne", "correctAnswer": "where", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Adverbs - Part 1" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "kifindirgi", "correctAnswer": "why", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Adverbs - Part 1" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "kifinosi", "correctAnswer": "how", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Adverbs - Part 1" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "ishish", "correctAnswer": "maybe", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Adverbs - Part 1" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "disse", "correctAnswer": "only", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Adverbs - Part 1" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "sille", "correctAnswer": "next", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Adverbs - Part 1" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "ahhaz", "correctAnswer": "then", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Adverbs - Part 1" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "save", "correctAnswer": "again", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Adverbs - Part 1" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "kash", "correctAnswer": "while", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Adverbs - Part 1" });

	/* LESSON 5, Adverbs - Part 2 */
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "dei", "correctAnswer": "light", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Adverbs - Part 2" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "ao", "correctAnswer": "dark", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Adverbs - Part 2" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "rekke", "correctAnswer": "there", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Adverbs - Part 2" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "jinne", "correctAnswer": "here", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Adverbs - Part 2" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "yath", "correctAnswer": "up", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Adverbs - Part 2" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "zohhe", "correctAnswer": "down", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Adverbs - Part 2" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "asshekh", "correctAnswer": "today", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Adverbs - Part 2" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "silokh", "correctAnswer": "tomorrow", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Adverbs - Part 2" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "ajjalan", "correctAnswer": "tonight", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Adverbs - Part 2" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "ajjin", "correctAnswer": "now", "m": 1, "level": 3, "levelTitle": "Adjectives and Adverbs", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Adverbs - Part 2" });


/*---------- LEVEL 4, VERBS PART 1 ----------*/
	/* LESSON 1, Dothraki Life */
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "lirat", "correctAnswer": "to tattoo", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Dothraki Life" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "vindelat", "correctAnswer": "to stab", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Dothraki Life" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "zireyeselat", "correctAnswer": "to offend", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Dothraki Life" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "zhilat", "correctAnswer": "to love", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Dothraki Life" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "addrivat", "correctAnswer": "to kill", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Dothraki Life" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "astilat", "correctAnswer": "to joke about", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Dothraki Life" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "emrasolat", "correctAnswer": "to raid", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Dothraki Life" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "fakat", "correctAnswer": "to kick", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Dothraki Life" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "fatilat", "correctAnswer": "to insult", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Dothraki Life" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "drivolat", "correctAnswer": "to die from", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Dothraki Life" });

	/* LESSON 2, Actions with Animals */
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "vishaferat", "correctAnswer": "to break a horse", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Actions with Animals" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "addakhat", "correctAnswer": "to feed", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Actions with Animals" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "dothralat", "correctAnswer": "to ride alongside", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Actions with Animals" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "drogat", "correctAnswer": "to drive animals", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Actions with Animals" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "drozhat", "correctAnswer": "to slay", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Actions with Animals" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "govat", "correctAnswer": "to breed", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Actions with Animals" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "hakelat", "correctAnswer": "to name", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Actions with Animals" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "javrathat", "correctAnswer": "to rein", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Actions with Animals" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "karlinat", "correctAnswer": "to gallop beside", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Actions with Animals" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "ogat", "correctAnswer": "to slaughter an animal", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Actions with Animals" });

	/* LESSON 3, Actions on Objects */
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "ammenat", "correctAnswer": "to empty something", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Actions on Objects" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "annevalat", "correctAnswer": "to leave something alone", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Actions on Objects" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "assamvat", "correctAnswer": "to break something", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Actions on Objects" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "avvirsalat", "correctAnswer": "to burn something", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Actions on Objects" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "avvitisherat", "correctAnswer": "to grow something", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Actions on Objects" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "azzohat", "correctAnswer": "to put something down", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Actions on Objects" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "akkovarat", "correctAnswer": "to stand something up", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Actions on Objects" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "emmalat", "correctAnswer": "to make something enter", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Actions on Objects" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "eqorasalat", "correctAnswer": "to let go of something", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Actions on Objects" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "eyelat", "correctAnswer": "to move something", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Actions on Objects" });

	/* LESSON 4, Power Dynamics */
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "arranat", "correctAnswer": "to shame", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Power Dynamics" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "chomolat", "correctAnswer": "to honor", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Power Dynamics" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "qoralat", "correctAnswer": "to seize", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Power Dynamics" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "ziganesolat", "correctAnswer": "to defy", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Power Dynamics" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "acchakat", "correctAnswer": "to silence", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Power Dynamics" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "annithat", "correctAnswer": "to cause pain", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Power Dynamics" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "assilat", "correctAnswer": "to defeat", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Power Dynamics" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "davrakh", "correctAnswer": "to be useful to", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Power Dynamics" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "echomosalat", "correctAnswer": "to dishonor", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Power Dynamics" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "iddelat", "correctAnswer": "to make someone drink", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Power Dynamics" });

	/* LESSON 5, The Body and the Senses */
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "charat", "correctAnswer": "to hear", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "The Body and the Senses" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "astolat", "correctAnswer": "to speak of", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "The Body and the Senses" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "frakhat", "correctAnswer": "to touch", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "The Body and the Senses" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "frakholat", "correctAnswer": "to feel", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "The Body and the Senses" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "rivvat", "correctAnswer": "to smell", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "The Body and the Senses" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "donat", "correctAnswer": "to shout about", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "The Body and the Senses" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "dogat", "correctAnswer": "to suffer from", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "The Body and the Senses" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "vineserat", "correctAnswer": "to remember", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "The Body and the Senses" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "akkoalat", "correctAnswer": "to heal", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "The Body and the Senses" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "garvolat", "correctAnswer": "to hunger from", "m": 1, "level": 4, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 1", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "The Body and the Senses" });


/*---------- LEVEL 5, VERBS - PART 2 ----------*/
	/* LESSON 1, Barbaric Actions */
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "achralat", "correctAnswer": "to be smelly", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Barbaric Actions" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "adakhilat", "correctAnswer": "to feed on", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Barbaric Actions" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "arrokhat", "correctAnswer": "to frighten", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Barbaric Actions" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "atthasat", "correctAnswer": "to destroy (insulting)", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Barbaric Actions" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "awazat", "correctAnswer": "to scream", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Barbaric Actions" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "donat", "correctAnswer": "to shout", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Barbaric Actions" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "drivolat", "correctAnswer": "to die", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Barbaric Actions" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "esittesak", "correctAnswer": "to brag", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Barbaric Actions" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "fejat", "correctAnswer": "to hate", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Barbaric Actions" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "fonat", "correctAnswer": "to hunt", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 1, "lessonTitle": "Barbaric Actions" });

	/* LESSON 2, Actions of a Healthy Lifestyle */
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "adakhat", "correctAnswer": "to eat", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Actions of a Healthy Lifestyle" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "anat", "correctAnswer": "to jog", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Actions of a Healthy Lifestyle" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "ammithrat", "correctAnswer": "to rest", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Actions of a Healthy Lifestyle" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "ammemat", "correctAnswer": "to play a musical instrument", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Actions of a Healthy Lifestyle" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "ezhirat", "correctAnswer": "to dance", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Actions of a Healthy Lifestyle" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "ezolat", "correctAnswer": "to learn", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Actions of a Healthy Lifestyle" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "hajolat", "correctAnswer": "to grow strong", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Actions of a Healthy Lifestyle" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "hoyalat", "correctAnswer": "to sing", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Actions of a Healthy Lifestyle" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "ifat", "correctAnswer": "to walk", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Actions of a Healthy Lifestyle" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "indelat", "correctAnswer": "to drink", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 2, "lessonTitle": "Actions of a Healthy Lifestyle" });

	/* LESSON 3, Actions of a Great Leader */
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "akkelenat", "correctAnswer": "to decide", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Actions of a Great Leader" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "assolat", "correctAnswer": "to command", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Actions of a Great Leader" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "dirgat", "correctAnswer": "to think", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Actions of a Great Leader" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "erin", "correctAnswer": "to be good", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Actions of a Great Leader" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "ezzolat", "correctAnswer": "to teach", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Actions of a Great Leader" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "gachat", "correctAnswer": "to solve", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Actions of a Great Leader" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "goshat", "correctAnswer": "to be certain", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Actions of a Great Leader" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "jerat", "correctAnswer": "to trade", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Actions of a Great Leader" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "jilat", "correctAnswer": "to be correct", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Actions of a Great Leader" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "koalat", "correctAnswer": "to be of help", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 3, "lessonTitle": "Actions of a Great Leader" });

	/* LESSON 4, Actions of Dothraki Women */
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "ammasat", "correctAnswer": "to decorate", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Actions of Dothraki Women" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "emat", "correctAnswer": "to smile", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Actions of Dothraki Women" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "annithilat", "correctAnswer": "to entice", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Actions of Dothraki Women" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "arannat", "correctAnswer": "to be neglected", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Actions of Dothraki Women" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "ayyolat", "correctAnswer": "to bear a child", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Actions of Dothraki Women" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "chakat", "correctAnswer": "to be silent", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Actions of Dothraki Women" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "charolat", "correctAnswer": "to listen", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Actions of Dothraki Women" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "chomat", "correctAnswer": "to be respectful", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Actions of Dothraki Women" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "ekhogaralat", "correctAnswer": "to undress", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Actions of Dothraki Women" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "jolinat", "correctAnswer": "to cook", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 4, "lessonTitle": "Actions of Dothraki Women" });

	/* LESSON 5, Other Useful Verbs */
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "aresat", "correctAnswer": "to hide", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Other Useful Verbs" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "arrissat", "correctAnswer": "to fix", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Other Useful Verbs" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "arthasat", "correctAnswer": "to fall", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Other Useful Verbs" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "astat", "correctAnswer": "to say", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Other Useful Verbs" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "astolat", "correctAnswer": "to speak", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Other Useful Verbs" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "atholat", "correctAnswer": "to dry", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Other Useful Verbs" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "chilat", "correctAnswer": "to lie down", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Other Useful Verbs" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "choqat", "correctAnswer": "to flee", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Other Useful Verbs" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "chorkat", "correctAnswer": "to roll", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Other Useful Verbs" });
	Question.create({"socketId": id, "prompt": "dinat", "correctAnswer": "to pass", "m": 1, "level": 5, "levelTitle": "Verbs - Part 2", "lesson": 5, "lessonTitle": "Other Useful Verbs" });
}

module.exports = createQuestions;